<resources>

    <string name="app_name">AgroSpread</string>

    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="settings_options">
        <item>Edit Profile</item>
        <item>Edit Email</item>
        <item>Edit Password</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="aboutus">     Welcome to AgroSpread, your trusted E-Commerce platform dedicated to empowering farmers and enhancing agricultural practices. Our mission is to connect farmers with high-quality agricultural products, tools, and equipment, making it easier than ever to thrive in today’s competitive landscape.

      At AgroSpread, we understand the challenges farmers face, from sourcing reliable supplies to managing costs. That’s why we offer a comprehensive selection of fertilizers, seeds, tools, and equipment—all curated to meet the diverse needs of agricultural professionals. Our user-friendly platform allows farmers to browse and purchase the products they need with just a few clicks, ensuring convenience and efficiency.

     We are committed to supporting sustainable farming practices and fostering a community where farmers can share knowledge and resources. Whether you’re a seasoned farmer or just starting out, AgroSpread is here to help you cultivate success.

      Join us in revolutionizing the agricultural supply chain and empowering farmers everywhere. Together, let’s grow a better future!</string>

    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>

    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be &gt;5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">Login failed</string>

    <string name="logout_message">Logout menu item clicked</string>
    <string name="logout_success">Logout successful</string>
</resources>
